Partheev Budarapu in

Partheev

Full Stack Web Developer

A guy with self-motivation and a passion for Computer Science. Have good experience working with teams and handling challenging problems in software development. I have 2+ years of experience in developing full-stack (MERN) web applications. I led teams while working on hackathons.

I follow the best practices and write clean code while working on projects. Have the ability to learn new things on the fly.

Experience

Frontend Intern / Intugine Technologies

July 2022 - Dec 2022

- Built a dashboard using Reactis and Material–UI to modify the client's configuration.
- API integrations

Full Stack Developer Intern / TechPranee

Mar 2022 – Sep 2022

- Worked on developing an e-commerce website, health care platform using Next.js, and Student Learning platform.
- Integrated third-party services like payment gateway, shiprocket (products shipments), firebase, and Google authentication.
- Handled modifications in existing client projects.

Achievements

IBM Hack Challenge 2022 Jury Award

Our team was declared the Runner-up team of the IBM Hack Challenge 2022, a national-level hackathon by IBM with 20,000 enrollments. I led our project as Team leader of my team, we developed and deployed Nutrition Assistant Mobile-First web app.

Flipr Hackathon XIII Winners

We were declared Winners by securing an A+ grade. Developed and deployed C2C (Customer to Customer) personal loan lending platform.

Skills

JavaScript • Typescript • React • Next.js • Node.js • Material-UI • MongoDB • PostgreSQL • Golang • Database Design • Docker • C++ • Full Stack Web Developer

Education

2020-2024

Computer Science and Technology / G. Pulla Reddy Engineering College, AP, India. CGPA: 8.4